<root>
   <meta title="Erlang Web Server Challenge"/>
   <meta tags="erlang,web,server,challenge,static,concurrency"/>
   <meta disabled="true"/>
   <sentences>
      <mayor>
         I hereby declare a challenge.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         It is a most noble contest of agility, speed, wits, and valor. Who dares accept the challenge?
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The challenge is to run tests on the most popular erlang web servers to see whose metal is hard and sharp and whose is brittle and weak.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The challenge is to test many web servers.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         I'm issuing a challenge to erlang warriors to see who can muster blinding speed and harness the awesome power of massive concurrency.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The rules are as follows: You must test one of the designated servers.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         You must serve a static file it must be 100 bytes.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         Strictly static.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         It must be erlang.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         You must read it from disk.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         Then you can serve it using whatever devilish alchemy you can devise.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The more arcane and clever, the better.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The challenge is hereby issued: go forth and bring me delightful numbers to tickle my fancy!
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         I will declare the victor at the end and have the loser beheaded to the jeers of the roaring crowd.
      </mayor>
      <mayor link="next">
         This displeases me.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         You are disqualified from the challenge.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         I shall post them in the town square for all to see.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         The victor will receive a parade in his honor, a seat at my table, and the choice cuts from my prized hog.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         Bloodsport, my dear boy: it's how Kings stay in power.
      </mayor>
      <mayor>
         It will be a tournament of epic proportion, my most daunting challenge yet!
      </mayor>
   </sentences>
   <characters>
      <mayor>
         <sig type="noun">Erlang Warriors</sig>
         <sig type="adj">blinding speed</sig>
         <sig type="noun">The awesome power of massive concurrency</sig>
         <sig type="adj">arcane and clever</sig>
         <sig type="sentence">Go forth and bring me delightful numbers to tickle my fancy!</sig>
         <sig type="sentence">Bloodsport, my dear boy: it's how Kings stay in power.</sig>
      </mayor>
   </characters>
</root>
